[Music] The
[âm nhạc]
flamboyant flowers bloom brightly, I return to sing. The village is bustling, the stream is opening,
hoa phượng nở đỏe sắc em về ca hát Rập
bringing so much
gian đầu khe hé lại sáng mang bao niềm
joy, resting after studying,
vui cùng nghỉ ngơi sau chăm lo học hành
and walking together in the green summer retreat.
cũng xanh bước đi khóa tu mùa hè
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Walking together in the green summer retreat, so
cùng xanh bước đi khóa tu mùa hè
much fun, learning good things. Living
vui thật nhiều học điều hay Sống ngay
honestly means doing good deeds in each summer,
thẳng là qua từng mùa hè làm việc thiện
cultivating karma, so much joy, learning good things,
tim tu nhân quả vui thật nhiều học đều
abandoning the thorns, that's the summer retreat, my friend,
hay bỏ lá cà là khóa tu mùa hè nào bạn
raise your hand! Singing la la la, having
ơi giơ cánh tay lên nào vui hát ca la là
fun, exchanging flowers, the
la vui với trao hoa
summer retreat, singing la la la, having fun, exchanging
khóa tu mùa hè vui hát ca la là la vui
goods, the
với Trao hàng
Bich Chau Ha,
Bích Châu Hà
summer retreat, singing la la la, having fun, exchanging
khóa tu mùa hè vui hát ca la là la vui
goods,
với Trao hàng
summer retreat.
khóa khóa tu mùa hè
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
flamboyant flowers bloom brightly, summer returns, singing loudly, the stream is opening,
hoa phượng nở đỏe sắc hè về ca hát râm
bringing so much
ran đầu khe hé lại sáng mang bao niềm
joy, resting after studying, and walking together in the green
vui cùng nghỉ ngơi sau chăm lo học hành
summer retreat. The
cùng xanh bước đi khóa tu mùa hè
green summer retreat, so
màu xanh bước đi khóa tu mùa hè
much fun, learning good things. Living
vui thật nhiều học điều hay Sống ngay
honestly means doing good deeds in the summer retreat,
thẳng là khóa tu mùa hè làm việc thiện
cultivating karma, so much joy, learning good things,
tin tu nhân quả vui thật nhiều học điều
abandoning the thorns, that's the summer retreat, my friend,
hay bỏ lá cà là khóa tu mùa hè nào bạn
raise your hand.  Raise your hands, let's sing la la la la, let's have
ơi giơ cánh tay lên nào vui ca la là la
fun! Giving away
lá vui biết Trao hàng
summer retreat supplies, singing la la la, having fun
khóa tu mùa hè vui hát ca la là la vui
with giving away
với Trao hàng
fun with giving away summer retreat supplies, singing la la la, having fun
khóa tung mùa hè vui hát ca la là la vui
summer retreat supplies
khóa tu mùa hè
[music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]